{
    "id": "3d9aae6b33e742d383889e20bfd76efe",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Though we are good friends, our views …….. in certain matters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "different",
                "differ",
                "differing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7afaa57e442a47949c62ff44fe1d26d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The President gave away the ……… awards at a special function.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gallant",
                "gallantry"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7edfb462f092474ca99c25180756b142"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge was not satisfied with the lawyer’s …………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "argue",
                "arguing",
                "argument"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f8222cb2713b45ab8ad9bed27b3a4387"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should be careful to preserve the …………. of the religious places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sanction",
                "sanctify",
                "sanctity"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "653557aef68c42f4b100c7ae245585c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cricket match between India and Pakistan was an …………. one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excite",
                "excitement",
                "exciting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "35ca3ebef3d64f91ba645a3b49d37174"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of the road accidents ………….. as a result of careless driving .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occur",
                "occurring",
                "occurrence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e332dfae6324dd681f3f91ad20cb662"
        },
        {
            "question": "She cried …………. for help when she was attacked by robbers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "frantic",
                "frantical",
                "frantically"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a5787f453142498bbfbc6217d5f76690"
        },
        {
            "question": "Their ………… was proved wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "assume",
                "assumption"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e8d02cddc2834debba31ac69a5163c59"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 We had a ………… holiday by the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "delight",
                "delightful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52e8dd95fb3d4e75a38eb9eadd3d7f3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not like his ……….. behavior.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "insolence",
                "insolent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2dbdd934861e48a9a5c45f0a9f11b76b"
        }
    ]
}